otticanet.com 2019-04-06

# Privacy Policy - Otticanet.com

We are committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy describes the types of information we collect from you when you use the Otticanet.com site, and explains what we do with that information. Except as described in this policy, we do not sell, trade or rent your personal information to third parties. Keep in mind, you always have the option to unsubscribe of our email program at anytime.

This Privacy Policy is effective as of February 2017 and will remain in effect until we replace it.

**What kind of information do we collect?**

We may collect and store personal information from you, such as your name, email address, postal address, phone number, gender, birthday, personal interests, product reviews and ratings, etc., when you create an account with us, place an order online, contact us with a question or concern, subscribe to our newsletter or participate in a contest, promotion, or survey. We maintain a record of your product interests and the purchases you make online.   
We collect and store certain other information automatically whenever you interact with this Website. For example, we may collect your IP address, browser information, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data and reference site domain name. We also collect information regarding customer traffic patterns and site usage. To view our complete cookie policy please click here.

**How do we use your information?**

To process and fulfill your order, including to send you emails to confirm your order status and shipment, and other related emailsTo communicate with you and to send you information by email or other means about our products, services, surveys, contests, and promotions, unless you have directed us not to contact you with promotional communications via our opt-out procedure

  * To administer and fulfill our contests and other promotions
  * To help us address problems with and improve our site design, products and services
  * To analyze trends and statistics as well as your shopping preferences.
  * To protect the security or integrity of our Websites and our business
  * To contact you if necessary

**Whom do we share information with?**

We engage third parties to perform services in connection with the operation of our business. Examples of these services include payment processing and authorization, order fulfillment and shipping, marketing, website evaluation and data analysis. We provide personal information to these third parties, but we authorize them to use this information only in connection with the services they perform. These parties may also collect information directly from your use of our site, but we prohibit them from using such information in anything other than an aggregated non-personal form.We may share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. Aggregate demographic information is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.  
We may release personal information if we believe in good faith that we are required to do so by law or that such release is necessary to protect the rights, property or safety of Otticanet.com, or any of our affiliates, business partners, customers or others.  
As with any business, it is possible that we might go through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition, sale of all or a portion of our assets, or sell or buy other assets. In such transactions, information about customers often is among the transferred assets. You will be notified via a prominent notice on our site for 30 days of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information. You consent to the transfer of your personally identifiable information to any such successor entity unless you notify us via email to the contrary.

**Unsubscription**

You always have the option to unsubscribe from our email program or  cancel "Your Account" at anytime. If at any time you no longer wish to have Otticanet contact you, or to receive information, emails or notices from otticanet.com or our partners, simply unsubscribe here. Also, you will always have the right to access, modify or delete information in "Your Account.

**Minors**

Our Site is not intended for use by children under the age of 14, and we do not target or collect personal information from children under the age of 14. We encourage parents to be active in regulating their child's online activities and interests appropriately.

**Links**

Links to third party web sites on our Site are provided solely as a convenience to you. If you use these links, you will leave our Site. We have not reviewed all of these third party sites and do not control and are not responsible for any of these sites, their content or their privacy policy. If you decide to access any of the third party sites linked to our Site, you do so at your own risk.

OTTICANET - [Star Usa, Inc](https://starusainc.com/)

Headquarters: 109 East 17th Street Suite 420 - Cheyenne - WY - 82001

Support & Returns: C/O Export Usa, 18 Bridge St. Unit 2A - Brooklyn - NY - 11201

E-mail: info@otticanet.com - Telephone: +1 (307) 220-4280 ****
